This type is a Pierrot capelet.
And as I discussed earlier, the Pierrot part of it comes from this pointy clown like clown suit aspect of the garment.
The capelet part of it is because it's going to be set on top and go down the shoulders like a capelet.
Right here we have where it attaches.
What this is doing in the drawing is going to be a separate flouncy piece as the capelet, sewn to the garment here and then also done with a zipper.
That just creates something that has more design lines on it than anything else.
But the capelet part is not unattached anymore.
So technically this is what it's called but it's one whole piece of whatever it is, shirt that you're doing.
It just has several different variations.
Different ways of opening it per say.